all right it's 5:30 so I'll get started
好吧，现在是5:30，所以我开始
I'm Christine flood I work for Red Hat
我是Christine Flood，我在Red Hat工作
we've developed a low pause garbage
我们开发了低停顿垃圾
collector and this is a little bit about
收藏家，这是关于
garbage collection a lot about
垃圾收集很多
Shenandoah and then a little bit about
雪兰多厄，然后关于
what we're doing in Shenandoah 2.0
我们在雪兰多ah 2.0中做什么
Shenandoah 1.0 is out there for
Shenandoah 1.0在那里
everybody that uses rail or Fedora or
每个使用rail或Fedora或
any Linux distribution built off of
任何基于Linux构建的发行版
those but it's not up an open JDK yet so
那些，但是还没有开放的JDK，所以
I have these little star slides if you
我有这些小星星幻灯片，如果你
like get lost and wait for the next star
喜欢迷路，等待下一颗星星
you can get back on track and it's also
您可以回到正轨，而且
a queue to me to breathe because
排我呼吸，因为
otherwise I talk way too fast so if you
否则我讲得太快了，所以如果你
were here for the last talk we're gonna
在这里是我们要进行的最后一次谈话
talk a little bit about traditional semi
谈一些传统的半
space collectors and then we're gonna
太空收藏家，然后我们要
talk about region based collectors like
谈论基于区域的收藏家，例如
Jiwon and Shenandoah we're gonna talk
智元和雪兰多我们要谈谈
about the Shenandoah however of them
关于雪兰多
we're gonna give you some results I'm
我们要给你一些结果，我
gonna give a brief demo of a visualizer
给一个可视化工具的简短演示
that lets you watch your keep while
让您一边看守
you're allocating and garbage collecting
你正在分配和垃圾收集
and it can give you a clue as to how to
它可以为您提供有关如何
better optimize your garbage collection
更好地优化您的垃圾收集
algorithm for your application and then
您的应用程序的算法，然后
I'm going to talk about what's next what
我要说的是下一个什么
are we working on now that we've got
现在我们正在努力吗
this working so traditional semi space
如此传统的半空间
garbage collection algorithms if you
垃圾收集算法，如果您
were here for Gil's talks you saw a lot
在这里为吉尔的演讲你看到了很多
of this I'll give a little bit more
我会再给你一点
detail I think so they break the heap up
我认为细节，所以他们把堆弄碎了
into young and old generation and they
进入年轻一代和老一代，他们
use a card table to keep track of the
使用卡片表来跟踪
pointers from the old to the new so here
从旧到新的指针，所以在这里
you can see that we've created an object
您可以看到我们已经创建了一个对象
foo in the old generation and it points
上一代的foo及其指向
to bar as soon as we write that pointer
写完指针后立即禁止
to bar in we have to make a mark in the
禁止进入，我们必须在
card table and that's how we keep track
牌桌，这就是我们保持追踪的方式
of all them pointers from old to young
在所有这些中，从老年到青年的指针
and this is for serial parallel part of
这是用于串行并行部分
new CMS they all keep track of a card
新的CMS，他们都跟踪卡片
table this way to keep track of the
用这种方式来记录
pointers so they can collect just the
指针，以便他们可以只收集
young generation in isolation so if your
孤立的年轻一代，所以如果你
objects are dying young this works great
对象快要死了，这很棒
because you're collecting all of the all
因为你正在收集所有
of the dead stuff out of the end
死了的东西
generation without ever having to look
一代无需看
at this big old generation
在这个大老一辈
however we've moved on to region based
但是我们已经转向基于区域
collectors like Jiwon and rather than
智元这样的收藏家而不是
having a dedicated old generation and a
有敬业的老一辈
young generation they divide the heap up
年轻的一代，他们把堆分开
into regions and we allocate in regions
进入区域，然后在区域中进行分配
sometimes we have objects that are too
有时我们也有物体
big to fit in the region and those are
大到适合该地区的那些
humongous and they're dealt with
巨大，他们被处理
specially but mostly we allocate objects
特别但主要是我们分配对象
and regions and then when it comes time
和地区，然后是时候
to garbage collect we can copy the live
垃圾收集我们可以复制现场
objects to a new region so here we've
反对一个新的地区，所以我们在这里
got two regions full of objects some of
有两个充满物体的区域
which that are dead we copy the live
那些死了的我们复制现场
objects over and then we can have those
对象结束，然后我们可以拥有那些
two objects those two regions free to
这两个区域可以自由活动的两个物体
continue allocating in and all of our
继续分配，我们所有
objects have been compacted so we don't
对象已经被压缩，所以我们不
necessarily have to have the 50%
一定要有50％
overhead that a 70 space collector would
70个太空收集器会产生的开销
have so g1 it's the best of my knowledge
有g1这是我所知
the last time I looked at it which I
我最后一次看的时候
feel right I should probably should have
感觉正确，我应该应该有
given a caveat awhile ago I worked on g1
不久前我做了一个警告，我研究了g1
when it was an original just an idea and
当它是原始的只是一个想法，
I haven't really looked at it lately but
我最近还没真正看过
back then we had a card table to keep
那时候我们有一张桌子
track of old to young references and we
跟踪从老到小的参考文献，我们
had remembered sets for keeping track of
记得记得跟踪
old to old references so if you have a
旧到旧参考，所以如果您有一个
pointer from food a bar in the old
从食物指针在旧酒吧
generation you have to do the mark in
一代，你必须做标记
the card table like I said and this says
像我说的卡片表，这说
that we can collect all the young
我们可以收集所有的年轻人
regions by just looking at the young
只是看着年轻人
regions or root set and the card table
区域或根集以及卡表
but if we make them our region pointer
但是如果我们将它们设为区域指针
from an old region to an old region we
从一个古老的地区到一个古老的地区
have to store that location in a
必须将该位置存储在
remembrance set and that's how we can
纪念套装，这就是我们可以做到的
collect just the old region that
只收集旧的地区
collects foo without looking at the
收集foo而无需查看
entire Hiba so this is sort of giving
整个希巴，所以这有点
you a background so when I talk to you
你的背景，所以当我和你说话时
about how we're doing this in China Noah
关于我们在中国如何做到这一点
it'll make sense another way to look at
这将是另一种看待方式
this is this is this is sort of
这是这个
demonstrating what the garbage
展示什么垃圾
collectors are doing so we have these
收藏家在做，所以我们有这些
card tables and these remembrance sets
牌桌和这些纪念套
and that allows us to do things like we
这样我们就可以做像我们这样的事情
can have a young generation pause and
可以让年轻一代停下来
another young generation pause then we
另一个年轻一代停下来，然后我们
can do the
可以做到
concurrent mark and figure out all the
并发标记并找出所有
stuff that's live that's not in young
不年轻的生活中的东西
generation regions and then we can do a
生成区域，然后我们可以
mixed collection in g1 so Shenandoah is
g1中的混合集合，所以雪兰多是
different we still do the concurrent
不同的是我们仍然做并发
marking that they do but we copy the
标记他们这样做，但我们复制了
objects of all the Java threads are
所有Java线程的对象是
running so here you can say we still
运行，所以在这里你可以说我们仍然
have stopped the world pauses but
已经停止了世界的停顿，但是
they're much much shorter so concurrent
它们要短得多，所以并发
marking is hard and I think if you were
标记很难，我想如果
here for Gil's talk he described it as
在吉尔的演讲中，他形容为
pointers behind you I'm gonna describe
我要描述的是你身后的指针
it a little kind of the same way so if
有点一样，所以如果
you have a and a points to be you mark a
你有一个和一个点，你要标记一个
and you mark B if after you've marked a
如果标记为a，则标记为B
that pointer moves down to point to D
指针向下移动以指向D
and the point of the pointed to D points
指向D点的点
to B we now have this object D over here
到B我们现在在这里有这个物体D
that's live and is never going to get
那是活的，永远不会得到
marked because the marking the the front
标记是因为标记在前面
line of the marking has moved past it
标记线已移过它
and so what snapshot at the beginning
那么一开始的快照是什么
does is it says that anything that was
是不是说那是什么
live at the beginning is still alive
刚开始还活着
so we know that D is alive sorry and we
所以我们知道D还在世，我们
know that D is alive so we add D to a Q
知道D还活着，所以我们将D添加到Q
and we know that we can come back
而且我们知道我们可以回来
afterwards so whenever you overwrite a
之后，每当您覆盖一个
pointer you stash the old value on a q
您将旧值存储在aq上的指针
and that way you can make sure that
这样您可以确保
you've marked the entire heap anything
您已经标记了整个堆
that's newly allocated is considered
新分配的被认为
live as well so here we have the stuff
生活得很好，所以这里有东西
that's unique to Shenandoah which is
这是雪伦多亚所独有的
concurring evacuation so you have a
同时撤离，所以你有一个
problem and the problem with concurrent
问题和并发问题
evacuation is that you're competing
疏散是你在竞争
between the garbage collector that wants
想要的垃圾收集器之间
to copy objects and the Java threads
复制对象和Java线程
that want to write two objects so here
要写两个对象，所以在这里
you can see that the GC thread wants to
您可以看到GC线程想要
copy a with its field of Fred and the
复制带有Fred和其字段的
javathread wants to write to the object
javathread要写入对象
and it wants to update the thread to
它想将线程更新为
point to Bob so if you're not careful
指向鲍勃，所以如果你不小心的话
and you don't do things carefully you
你不小心做事
can end up with a copy of your object
可以得到对象的副本
that doesn't include the latest writes
不包括最新的文章
and the way we solve that in Shenandoah
以及我们在雪兰多解决问题的方式
is that we copy the objects first and
是我们首先复制对象，然后
then we perform the right
然后我们执行正确的
so here the javathread has to copy a and
所以在这里javathread必须复制一个和
then perform the right so the other
然后执行正确的，所以另一个
problem with concurrent evacuation is
同时疏散的问题是
keeping track of which copy is the real
跟踪哪个副本是真实的
copy of a right because I now have two
权利的副本，因为我现在有两个
copies of a in my Heat so I have an
的副本在我的热火中，所以我有一个
indirection pointer this is probably the
间接指针，这可能是
most controversial part of shenandoah
申南多最有争议的部分
well maybe they're not being
好吧，也许他们不是
generational exactly but by adding an
完全是世代相传的，但是添加了
extra pointer to an object it allows us
指向对象的额外指针，它允许我们
to move the objects while the Java
在Java中移动对象
threads are running just by updating the
线程仅通过更新
indirection pointer so I could have 17
间接指针，所以我可以有17
things pointing to a and once I cast
指向的东西，一旦我投放
that pointer to point to the new a prime
指向新素数的指针
everything else will read through the
其他所有内容都将通过
interaction pointer and get the new copy
交互指针并获取新副本
all at once and the way that happens is
一下子就发生了
with a read barrier so in the regular
有阅读障碍，所以在常规
compiler you will read the location of
编译器您将读取位置
foo so you know that foo lives in a
foo，所以您知道foo生活在
certain address and say ok I'm going to
某个地址，然后说好，我要去
read that address plus whatever the
读那个地址加上任何
field offset is which shenandoah what
场偏移量是哪个shenandoah什么
happens is you read the field before the
发生的情况是您在阅读之前
pointer to foo and that tells you where
指向foo的指针，它告诉您在哪里
foo really lives so most of the time it
foo大部分时间都活着
just points down to the object below it
指向下方的对象
and warms up your cache for you but
并为您预热缓存，但是
sometimes it means that you have to go
有时候，这意味着你必须去
somewhere else to find foo and then you
在其他地方找到foo然后你
have to go to offset from that somewhere
必须去抵消那个地方
else so results this is the
否则结果是
elasticsearch benchmark that I wrote
我写的elasticsearch基准
it's not out there for everybody to try
不是所有人都可以尝试的
so you can be a little skeptical but I
所以你可能会有些怀疑，但是我
to be honest I indexed a big data from
老实说我索引了一个大数据
common crawl which is the source of big
常见的爬网是大来源
data I looked at all the Wikipedia
我看过所有维基百科的数据
queries and I index them using elastic
查询，我使用弹性索引它们
search and you can see that here
搜索，您可以在这里看到
shenandoah versus g1 I don't want to
shenandoah与g1我不想
throw anything at you one I was on the
向我扔东西给你
original g1 paper g1 is a great
原装g1纸g1很棒
collector for what it does but in terms
收集者对其所做的事情，但就其而言
of Enda and run time it beats
的Enda和它击败的运行时间
and it will always beat us because we're
它会永远打败我们，因为我们
going through that interaction pointer
通过该交互指针
except on very specialized workloads but
除了非常专业的工作负载外，
in terms of total pause times were
就总暂停时间而言
significantly shorter we have paused the
明显缩短了，我们暂停了
world for all of five hundred twenty
五百二十的世界
milliseconds whereas they pause the work
毫秒，而他们暂停工作
well for four seconds our average pause
我们平均停顿了四秒钟
times are in order of magnitude better
时间好多了
our max past times you can see here 679
我们最大的过去时间，您可以在这里看到679
milliseconds versus 30 milliseconds
毫秒与30毫秒
we've we've succeeded in solving the
我们已经成功解决了
positon problem we do have more pauses
positon问题，我们确实有更多的停顿
so right now the time to save point that
所以现在该节省点时间了
Gail was talking about is a problem for
盖尔在说的是一个问题
us we have found in some cases that the
我们在某些情况下发现
time to save point is longer than the
保存时间比
time where we're actually doing GC work
我们实际进行GC工作的时间
and we have some ideas for how to
我们对如何
possibly fix that but I think that when
可能会解决这个问题，但我认为
you get to that point you know that
你到那个点，你知道
you've succeeded here's my favorite
你成功了，这是我的最爱
benchmark and it's Gil says he's never
基准，而吉尔说他从来没有
seen something like this in production
在生产中看到过类似的东西
and probably not but I have talked to
可能不是，但我已经与
people who have this problem right if
有这个问题的人，如果
they have a they had at least recently
他们有一个，至少最近有
used web cache so they would they would
使用了网络缓存，所以他们会
have a URL that pointed to like a
有一个指向像
gigabyte of data and they would fill up
千兆字节的数据，它们会填满
a table with URLs and then when they had
带有网址的表格，然后
to add one when there was no more space
在没有更多空间时添加一个
they got rid of the oldest one and in
他们摆脱了最古老的
that case generational garbage
那样的世代垃圾
collection losses it's one of those
收款损失是其中之一
cases where you're so used to this tool
习惯于此工具的情况
working for you and then you come into a
为你工作，然后你进入
situation where the weak generational
弱势一代的情况
hypothesis does not hold and then you're
假设不成立，那么你
like what happened oh my gosh so for
就像发生了什么事，哦，天哪，所以
this case shenandoah can really kick
这种情况下shenandoah真的可以踢
butt because we don't assume anything
对接，因为我们不承担任何责任
about the lifetimes of our objects so
关于我们物体的寿命
here our runtime is significantly faster
在这里，我们的运行时间明显更快
our pause times are significantly faster
我们的暂停时间明显更快
it's a total GC pause times 17 seconds
总GC暂停时间为17秒
versus 210 milliseconds
与210毫秒
our max GC pause of 235 milliseconds
我们的最大GC暂停时间为235毫秒
versus 12 milliseconds and we even have
与12毫秒相比，我们甚至拥有
fewer pauses because
更少的停顿，因为
our puzzles are more productive right we
我们的难题更有效
have all the stuff that's all dead in
拥有所有已死的东西
the Orion regions that we can get rid of
我们可以摆脱的猎户座地区
very quickly we don't have to do as many
很快，我们不必做太多
of them so just to be fair I wrote a
为了公平起见，我写了一个
benchmark that did generational trees
做世代树的基准
where you allocate one megabyte trees
在其中分配一兆字节的树
and discard them this is sort of perfect
抛弃它们，这是完美的
for the generational hypothesis because
对于世代假设，因为
these things are dying in the young
这些东西在年轻时正在消亡
generation and never getting promoted
一代，永不升职
we're not that much worse
我们并没有那么糟糕
we're a couple of seconds worse our GC
我们的GC差了几秒钟
pauses are still better because we're
停顿还是更好，因为我们
doing in the evacuation concurrently but
同时进行疏散，但
this is sort of a worst case for us and
这对我们来说是最坏的情况，
you can see that our max pause time is
您可以看到我们的最大暂停时间是
only a little bit less than theirs and
只比他们少一点
we do more of them so our average is
我们做更多的事情，所以我们的平均值是
lower that's how come we end up with
降低这就是我们最终得到的结果
less total but basically this is the
总数较少，但基本上这是
worst case for us so status we are
对我们来说，最糟糕的情况是
shipping if you have rel 74 or better or
如果您有rel 74或更高的价格，或者
Fedora 24 or better all you have to do
Fedora 24或更高的功能
is add dash X X colon + u shenandoah GC
是加破折号XX冒号+ u shenandoah GC
is this being recorded okay you're mine
记录下来好吗，你是我的吗
um and you can go into our wiki page to
嗯，您可以进入我们的Wiki页面来
get more information about it about how
获得有关它的更多信息
to play with it and there's a lot of
玩它，有很多
information that alexey shavelev has put
阿列克谢·沙夫列夫（Alexey Shavelev）提交的信息
up on how to to tune it if you want to
如果您想了解如何调整它
tune it but it runs pretty well right
调整它，但是它运行得很好
out of the box with just that argument
开箱即用
okay the visualizer let's see if I can
好，可视化器让我们看看是否可以
do this without losing everything
做到这一点而不会失去一切
okay ah that's not getting the sweater
好吧，那没有拿到毛衣
there
那里
okay it's very pretty on my screen but
好的，它在我的屏幕上非常漂亮，但是
that doesn't help you all right there is
那对你没有帮助
a visualizers out there that you can go
一个可视化工具在那里，你可以去
if you go to our website and look at it
如果您访问我们的网站并进行查看
you can download it and you can watch
你可以下载它，你可以看
what's going on
这是怎么回事
so what's next this is the alleged topic
所以接下来是所谓的话题
of my talk and it's probably gonna be a
在我的演讲中，可能会成为
little bit short feel free to ask any
有点短随时问任何
questions you still won't have yes I
问题你仍然不会是我
[Music]
[音乐]
have been could you come up and help me
你一直可以帮我吗
figure out why I lost my display and I'm
弄清楚为什么我丢了显示器而我
gonna say this um I got I got taken out
会说这个我让我被淘汰了
to the woodshed I originally stated it
我最初说的是在木棚上
was for 16 megabyte heaps and more but
用于16兆字节的堆以及更多，但是
my current language is the same
我目前的语言是一样的
predictable pause times from two
可预测的两次暂停时间
gigabytes to 200 gigabytes so it the
千兆字节到200千兆字节
what what when you look at the pause
当你看着暂停时会怎样
times rate it's a second per gigabyte
倍率是每千兆字节每秒
perhaps that's just a rule of thumb that
也许这只是一个经验法则
was in the previous talk but if you can
在上一次谈话中，但如果可以
sustain a pause time for the size of
保持暂停时间为
your heap right if you have a 250
如果您有250，那么您的堆就对了
megabyte heat you can do a full GC on
兆字节的热量，您可以在
that heap in milliseconds so you don't
该堆以毫秒为单位，因此您不必
really want to pay the overhead of
真的很想支付
shenandoah so it all depends on where
shenandoah所以这一切都取决于哪里
your pain point is at what point are the
你的痛点是在什么时候
pause times too long for you to tolerate
暂停时间过长，您无法忍受
and that's when you want to look at
那就是当你想看看
something like Shenandoah
像雪兰多
CMS is not a compacting collector we are
CMS不是我们的压缩收集器
we are we're compacting things
我们正在压缩东西
concurrently so we do not have that
同时发生，所以我们没有那个
issue I cannot say that we never hit a
问题我不能说我们从不打
full GC but we okay so this was another
完整的GC，但我们还可以，所以这是另一个
argument that I had this one I won we
我拥有这个我赢得了我们的争论
have the ability to do a full GC if you
有能力做一个完整的GC，如果你
need it if everything is is dead but if
如果一切都死了就需要它，但是如果
you are in a process of concurrent
您正在同时进行
marking and you're almost done
标记，您几乎完成了
we'll finish concurrent marking start a
我们将完成并发标记开始
concurrent evacuation and then let you
同时疏散，然后让你
guys go so stopping the world is only a
伙计们去，所以停止世界只是一个
worst-case scenario or if you call
最坏的情况或您致电
system that GC then we will give you the
GC的系统，那么我们将为您提供
ability to do a stop the world and have
能够阻止世界并拥有
a completely clean heap before you want
想要之前完全干净的堆
to start a benchmark or something but
开始一个基准之类的，但是
full G C's should be they could have
完整的G C应该是他们可以拥有的
been we could have left them out we
否则我们本可以把他们排除在外
could have left them out and throttled
本可以把他们排除在外而节流
the allocator and kept going but we I
分配器，并继续前进，但我们我
personally think that you rather have a
个人认为您宁愿拥有
full GC than the throttled allocator but
完整的GC比限制分配器
if you'd rather have a throttled
如果您想节制
allocator speak up and let me know
分配器说出来，让我知道
in
在
okay we have a flag that lets you do
好吧，我们有一个标志可以让您
that I don't remember it off the top of
我不记得它的顶部
my head but it there is a flag that says
我的头，但有一个标志说
that fools you see is not a fold you see
你看到的傻瓜不是你看到的褶皱
it's a concurrent chasing and it will
这是一个并发的追逐，它将
throttle you mutator because your beauty
阻止你的变种人，因为你的美丽
toes are stuck they can't allocate but I
脚趾被卡住了，无法分配，但我
would argue that if your mutators can't
会争辩说，如果您的增变者不能
allocate you know they might as well be
分配你知道他们可能也是
stopped right if they're stopped at an
如果他们停在一个
allocation point they're stopped
他们停止分配点
regardless
而不管
if our concurrent mark is in progress so
如果我们的并发标记正在进行中，那么
we've gotten some data already
我们已经有一些数据
we will not throw that away we will
我们不会抛弃我们
finish our concurrent mark and keep
完成我们的并发标记并保留
going it's only the case that if for
只有在这种情况下
some reason now I'm talking out of my
现在出于某种原因我在说我的话
eye
眼睛
we don't need to do full GCS but they're
我们不需要做完整的GCS，但是
there and you can disable them if you
在那里，如果您可以禁用它们
want to I guess as the is the bottom
我想因为底部是
line
线
that's true but so you say you don't got
是的，但是你说你没有
you guys don't do the fool she sees ever
你们不要做她见过的傻瓜
and I'm wondering does that harm your
我想知道这是否会伤害您
benchmarking numbers because you never
基准数字，因为您从不
have a fully compacted heap okay
有一个完全压缩的堆好吗
all right um where was I
好吧，我在哪里
you get to the right slide
您会转到正确的幻灯片
so and I lost it again I'm sorry I can't
所以我又丢了我很抱歉我不能
we can't stay on the right slide and I
我们不能停留在正确的幻灯片上，而我
have 11 minutes so being don't fix this
有11分钟，所以不要解决这个问题
we'll talk to you a little bit about
我们会和您谈谈
where other than having I'm gonna show a
除了让我展示一个
picture of this in a minute but rather
在一分钟内的图片，但是
than having a card table
比拥有卡牌桌
I want this slide to be the one that we
我希望这张幻灯片成为我们的幻灯片
see okay this is and when you brought it
知道了，这是当您带来时
up before it came to the inside and so I
在它进入内部之前，所以我
went back to here to find where I was
回到这里去找我
going and then I lost it if you want
去，然后我就把它丢了
this slide to be there yes
这张幻灯片在那里
what we have is sort of a very very
我们拥有的是非常非常
coarse one one item entry that we keep
我们保留的一项粗略条目
to keep track of pointers between
跟踪之间的指针
regions and we call it a connection
地区，我们称之为联系
matrix so we don't have designated old
矩阵，所以我们没有指定旧
regions and young regions what we do
地区和青年地区我们做什么
have here we go so here when I talked
在这里，我们走到这里，当我说话时
about g1 I talked about the remembered
关于g1我谈到了想起的
sets in the card table and how you have
设置在卡片表中以及您的状态
different things for keeping track of
跟踪不同的事物
what points to what we have one thing we
什么指向我们拥有的一件事，我们
call a connection matrix and all that
调用连接矩阵等
keeps track of is pointers from region
跟踪来自区域的指针
to region so we still have a rate
到区域，所以我们仍然有一个费率
barrier at the rate barrier rates a
障碍率a
single entry in the connection matrix to
连接矩阵中的单个条目
tell you these regions are connected so
告诉你这些区域是相连的
here you can see that region 3 points to
在这里您可以看到该区域3指向
region 1 and I've just written a pointer
区域1，我刚刚写了一个指针
into region 5 and that just means that
进入区域5，这意味着
we have to write a bit in our connection
我们必须在连接中写一些
matrix to say that they're connected and
表示他们已连接的矩阵，
this gives us the capability to choose
这使我们能够选择
regions that we want to collect and
我们要收集的区域和
collect them independently so if we want
独立收集它们，所以如果我们想要
to collect region 3 we have to go
收集区域3我们必须去
through our route set and we have to
通过我们的路线设置，我们必须
scan region 5 as a route set as part of
扫描区域5作为路由的一部分
the route set to collect region 3 so we
路线设置为收集区域3，所以我们
have new terminology that we're
有我们的新术语
introducing I can still remember back in
介绍我仍然记得
1998 when Steve Heller said this is
1998年，史蒂夫·海勒（Steve Heller）说这是
parallel and this is concurrent even
并行，甚至是并发的
though Hans Bowman said it the other way
虽然汉斯·鲍曼（Hans Bowman）则相反
around years ago but this is what we
大约几年前，但这就是我们
want to call we want to call our
想打电话给我们想打电话给我们
region's to collect our collection set
地区收集我们的收藏集
regions and we want to tell our regions
地区，我们想告诉我们的地区
to scan our roots our regions and so
扫描我们的根源我们的地区等等
we're just we're just
我们只是我们只是
treating our regions as another part of
将我们的地区视为另一部分
the route set so that we can do more
路线设置，以便我们可以做更多
collections so here what we do is we
收集，所以在这里我们要做的是
assign an allocation epoch to each of
为每个分配一个时期
our regions that says when the last
我们的地区说，当最后
allocation happened in that region and
分配发生在该地区，
that gives us the ability to do pretty
让我们有能力做漂亮的
much any kind of collection and strategy
几乎任何种类的收集和策略
that we want if we want to do a young
如果我们想做一个年轻的我们
collection here you can see region if we
在这里收集您可以看到地区，如果我们
want to put Region seven which is the
想把第七区
latest allocated region in our
我们最近分配的区域
collection set we can do it and we have
收藏集，我们可以做到，我们有
one pointer that points to it from
从它指向它的一个指针
region six so all we have to do is scan
区域六，所以我们要做的就是扫描
region 6 and then we can collect region
区域6然后我们可以收集区域
7 now this is more scanning work than if
7现在，与
it was just a card table right a region
那只是一个区域的纸牌桌
is bigger than a card but it's a lot
比卡片大，但很多
more flexible because it allows us to
更灵活，因为它使我们能够
treat old and young regions exactly the
准确地对待老旧地区
same and it allows us to define
一样，它允许我们定义
strategies that work for a young
适合年轻人的策略
generation for an application that needs
为需要的应用程序生成
a young generation or we could also do
年轻的一代，或者我们也可以做
it for an old generation we could
对于一代人来说，我们可以
collect the oldest generation by simply
只需收集最老的一代
scanning the one region the points to it
扫描一个区域到它的点
and so or we could go with the regions
所以我们可以选择地区
with the least number of references in
引用数量最少的
the least place places we need to update
最少我们需要更新的地方
so this is giving us the flexibility to
所以这给了我们灵活性
explore new cheesy policy and heuristics
探索新的俗气政策和启发式
this isn't you don't get this with well
这不是你做得不好
in Fodor yet this is still in
在福多尔，但这仍然在
experimental phases but we do have a
实验阶段，但我们确实有一个
stop the world partial collection
停止世界局部收藏
working and we are very close to having
工作，我们非常接近
incremental partial collection working
增量部分收集工作
sorry
抱歉
concurrent partial collection working
并发部分收集工作
the same forwarding pointer that we use
我们使用的相同转发指针
for the big collection we can use for a
对于大集合，我们可以使用
concurrent partial collection so we
并发部分收集，所以我们
won't be stopping to do young-jun
不会停止做俊俊
collections will just be stopping the
集合只会停止
world choosing our collection set and
世界选择我们的收藏集和
starting up again um another thing
再次开始，另一件事
missus I added this at the last minute
我在最后一分钟添加了这个
because I was afraid I wasn't gonna have
因为我怕我不会
enough time but it looks like I'm
有足够的时间，但看起来我
running out of time those rates five
那些时间用完了五个
fifty and six o'clock so we're
五点六点，我们
to skip this part so this is basically a
跳过这一部分，所以这基本上是一个
look at what Shenandoah 2.0 is going to
看看雪兰多亚2.0将会做什么
look like because we are doing these
看起来像是因为我们正在做这些
partial collections we can perform a
我们可以执行部分​​收集
collection without concurrent marking
没有并发标记的收集
information so we don't have to wait for
信息，所以我们不必等待
the full concurrent mark and that's as I
完整的并发标记，就是我
said like when you ran out of space and
就像当你用完空间
you couldn't do it you couldn't do a
你做不到，你做不到
full collection because you never cook
完整的收藏，因为你永远不会做饭
are marking data we can do these then
正在标记数据，我们可以做到这些
and so we can do an it partial and we
所以我们可以做一个局部的
can do a concurrent partial and we can
可以做一个并发的部分，我们可以
also do a concurrent mark and then a
也做一个并发标记，然后
concurrent evacuation which picks all of
同时疏散
the productive regions to collect if you
如果您要收集的生产区域
want more information again we have our
想要更多信息，我们有我们的
open JDK web page which has a wiki Java
打开具有Wiki Java的JDK网页
GC at Red Hat feel free to send
Red Hat的GC可随时发送
questions there and we'll get back to
问题在那里，我们将回到
you that goes to our whole team or you
整个团队的你还是你
can send directly to me CHF a redhead
可以直接向我发送CHF红发
comm I am looking for I'm having a hard
通讯，我正在寻找我正在努力
time um I'm in a containerized world and
时间，我在一个集装箱世界里
everybody wants to run in 200 megabytes
每个人都想以200兆字节运行
these days so if you have an application
这些天，所以如果你有申请
that runs in gigabytes and you have a GC
以千兆字节运行，并且您有一个GC
problem please get in contact with us we
问题，请与我们联系
want to work for you we want to be able
想要为您工作，我们希望能够
to show you that we can do that without
告诉你我们可以做到
stopping for more than a handful of
停下来不止几个
milliseconds any questions yes
毫秒任何问题是
we are shipping as a tech preview in 74
我们将在74中作为技术预览发布
we have had no problems so we should be
我们没有问题，所以我们应该
we are supported right
我们得到了支持
we are not behind an experimental
我们没有实验性的背后
options flag so Red Hat will support
options标志，因此Red Hat将支持
Shenandoah and rel and in fedora and
雪兰多和rel和浅顶软呢帽和
basically if you have a Linux
基本上，如果您有Linux
distribution that takes the RPMs from
从中获取RPM的分布
them will still support that the
他们仍然会支持
Shenandoah team still wants to hear from
雪兰多亚团队仍然希望听到
you we want to we want to have some
你我们想要我们想要一些
real-life user stories any other
真实的用户故事
questions yes
问题是
okay we haven't measured the connection
好吧，我们还没有测量连接
matrix at we're still right now we hit
现在我们仍然在打矩阵
we have ways we can make that smaller
我们有办法使它变小
but in terms of the shenandoah 1.0 our
但就shenandoah 1.0而言
only overhead is a word project so we're
只有开销是一个单词项目，所以我们
absolutely honest if you say - xmx port
如果你说的话绝对诚实-xmx port
gig you get four gig for your object
演出，您得到四场演出
space there's no there's no off to the
空间没有了
side data structures except for the
边数据结构，除了
bitmap but but there's there's no card
位图，但是没有卡
table there's no remember it said
桌子上不记得它说
there's none of that I can't say that
没有什么我不能说
it's more compact we actually do use
它实际上更紧凑了
more space write it but I can't tell you
有更多空间写，但我不能告诉你
how much more space unless I know your
除非我知道你还有多少空间
object size distribution right if you
对象大小分布权，如果您
have three very large objects and you
有三个非常大的物体，你
know our space that we take up as
知道我们占据的空间
minimal if all of your objects are you
如果你所有的对象都是你，那就最少
know have one value in them then then
知道其中有一种价值，然后
our overhead is large yes
我们的开销很大
if your we choose a collection set
如果您选择收藏集
before we enter into an evacuation phase
在我们进入疏散阶段之前
and if you write to an object that's in
如果您写入的对象是
one of these regions that has chosen to
这些地区之一选择
be evacuated the garbage collector will
撤离垃圾收集器
first evacuate the object and then write
首先撤离对象，然后编写
to it it no no it's it's not the la most
对此，不，不是，这不是最重要的
lightweight rate barrier in the world
世界上轻量级的利率障碍
but we have a very quick check of a
但我们很快检查了
thread local variable that says are we
线程局部变量说我们
in an evacuation phase and if you're not
在疏散阶段，如果你不这样做
then it doesn't do it so it's only most
然后它不会这样做，所以这只是大多数
of the time it's extremely quick and
在时间上非常快，
it's only when you're doing evacuation
只有当你疏散时
that you have to copy the object yes
您必须复制对象是
it is out of my control we are slated
这是我们无法控制的
for 10:00 but given what's going on with
10:00，但鉴于发生了什么
OpenJDK now and you know there's there
现在使用OpenJDK，您知道那里
I don't remember what's public and
我不记得什么是公开的
what's not but we are slated for 10:00
什么不是，但我们定于10:00
I don't know when ten is going to be so
我不知道十点什么时候会这样
I can't say when we're going to be put
我不能说我们什么时候被放
back upstream we are working in a 10:00
回到上游，我们在10:00
work space we have it out there we're
工作空间，我们在那里
hopeful anything else so yeah I told you
希望别的什么，所以我告诉你
I'd be done early thank you very much
我会早点完成的，非常感谢
for your time
在你的时间
[Applause]
[掌声]